ACTWU's Research Department Records 5619/016
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Lyntone Belts of P.R. Inc., 1971 (Box 63, Folder 99)
- M & B Manufacturing Co. (P.R.), 1969 (Box 63, Folder 100)
- MLW Corporation (P.R.), 1966-1970 (Box 63, Folder 101)
- McKnight Robes Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 63, Folder 102)
- Mal Eno Fabrics Inc. (P.R.), 1953-1955 (Box 63, Folder 103)
- Manhattan Hosiery Corp., 1970 (Box 63, Folder 104)
- Mansco International Corporation, 1962-1971 (Box 63, Folder 105)
- Sam Marber (Utuado Corp.) (P.R.), 1968 (Box 63, Folder 106)
- Marcar, Inc., of Puerto Rico, 1969-1970 (Box 63, Folder 107)
- Maria Mills, Inc., 1965-1969 (Box 63, Folder 108)
- Maria Mills. Inc., P.R., 1966 (Box 63, Folder 109)
- Manshirt. Inc., 1970 (Box 63, Folder 110)
- Manufacturas Ferrer Indumafer, Inc., 1973 (Box 63, Folder 111)
- Marferi, Inc., 1977 (Box 63, Folder 112)
- Margo Manufacturing., Corporation., 1968 (Box 63, Folder 113)
- Margo Manufacturing Corporation, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 114)
- Maria Slacks, Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 115)
- Mariane Draperies Corp., 1971 (Box 63, Folder 116)
- Maricao Mills, Inc., 1969 (Box 63, Folder 117)
- Marita Mills, Inc., 1961-1971 (Box 63, Folder 118)
- Marles, Incorporated (P.R.), 1953 (Box 63, Folder 119)
- Martinez- Fuentes, Inc.- Hato Rey, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 120)
- Marvel Glove Manufacturing Corp., (P.R.), 1967 (Box 63, Folder 121)
- Mate Originals, Inc., 1974 (Box 63, Folder 122)
- Matouk Industries, Inc., 1974 (Box 63, Folder 123)
- Maunabo Hosiery Mills Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 63, Folder 124)
- Mayquez Contracting Corporation., 1967 (Box 63, Folder 125)
- Mejia, Delia, Inc. (P.R.), 1958 (Box 63, Folder 126)
- Merit Pajama Corp., of Puerto Rico, 1960-1973 (Box 63, Folder 127)
- Merit Manufacturing Corporation, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 128)
- Don Meyers (Cidra, P.R.), 1967 (Box 63, Folder 129)
- Meyers & Son Manufacturing Co., of Puerto Rico., 1967-1971 (Box 63, Folder 130)
- Midland Knitting Mills Co., Inc., 1967 (Box 63, Folder 131)
- Miton Co., Inc., 1962-1971 (Box 63, Folder 132)
- Moca Mills, Inc. Puerto Rico, 1967-1973 (Box 63, Folder 133)
- Mohawk International, Inc. Aguadilla, Puerto Rico, 1966-1971 (Box 63, Folder 134)
- Mohawk Products Inc., 1965-1969 (Box 63, Folder 135)
- Moncho Manufacturing Corp., (P.R.), 1968 (Box 63, Folder 136)
- Morovis Manufacturing Company Division No. 2, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 137)
- Walter J. Mundy. Jr., 1966 (Box 63, Folder 138)
- My-Toy International, Inc., 1972 (Box 63, Folder 139)
- Max A. Nachman, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 140)
- Nazario, Ruben, D. (P.R.), 1958 (Box 63, Folder 141)
- Neckwear Corp. of Puerto Rico, 1954-1959 (Box 63, Folder 142)
- Leonard Goldberg (Needlework Corporation of America, Inc.), 1962 (Box 63, Folder 143)
- Richard C. Neek, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 144)
- New Continental Sportswear., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 145)
- Newberry Puerto Rico, Inc., 1969 (Box 63, Folder 146)
- Niko Manufacturing Company Inc., 1970 (Box 63, Folder 147)
- Federico Fernandez Noguera, 1964 (Box 63, Folder 148)
- Northridge Knitting Mills, Inc., 1967 (Box 63, Folder 149)
- Obalco Manufacturing Corporation, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder 150)
- Ocean Knitwear Corp., 1964 (Box 63, Folder 151)
- Pedro Ochoa, Sucr, Inc. (P.R.), 1955-1958 (Box 63, Folder 152)
- Oklahoma Clothing Manufacturings Inc. (P.R.), 1955 (Box 63, Folder 153)
- Olazco Manufacturing Corp. (P.R.), 1959-1964 (Box 63, Folder 154)
- Olimac Manufacturing Corporation., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 155)
- Olympic Mills Corp., 1960-1970 (Box 63, Folder 156)
- Ovejita, Inc., 1968 (Box 63, Folder 157)
- Orocovis Hosiery Mills Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 63, Folder 158)
- Overseas Sports Co., Inc. (P.R.), 1957-1974 (Box 63, Folder 159)
- P.L. Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 63, Folder 160)
- PM Footwear (Puerto Rico) (Box 63, Folder 161)
- P.R. Bootstraps Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1974 (Box 63, Folder 162)
- P.R.B. Underwear, Inc., 1974 (Box 63, Folder 163)
- P.R.B. Uniforms, Inc., 1974 (Box 63, Folder 164)
- Palmer Accessory Corporation., Inc. (P.R.), 1955 (Box 63, Folder 165)
- Palmer Santiago, R. Needlework (See San German Needlework Swiss Handloom) (P.R.), 1956 (Box 63, Folder 166)
- Pan American Knitwear, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 63, Folder 167)
- Pantalones Manso, Inc., 1973-1975 (Box 63, Folder 168)
- Paragon of Puerto Rico, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 169)
- John L. Parish, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 170)
- Park Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1962 (Box 63, Folder 171)
- Partex Corporation., Salina, P.R., 1966-1971 (Box 63, Folder 172)
- Patillas Hosiery Mills Inc. (Sub of Kayser Roth Intern. N.Y.), 1968-1971 (Box 63, Folder 173)
- Patillas Manufacturing Corporation, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 174)
- Fernando Pena, Inc. (P.R.), 1966 (Box 63, Folder 175)
- Penntex, Inc., 1974 (Box 63, Folder 176)
- Permatex Apparels, Inc., 1961 (Box 63, Folder 177)
- Philip Manufacturing Corporation., 1972 (Box 63, Folder 178)
- Piel Industria, Inc., 1973 (Box 63, Folder 179)
- Pilgrim Trousers, Inc. Las Piedras, (P.R.), 1966 (Box 63, Folder 180)
- Plastic Extruding & Printing Corp. ACWA, 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Plata Gloves Inc., 1961-1971 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Playmaster Co., Inc., 1959-1971 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Ponce Mills, Inc., 1963-1973 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Ponce Tanning Corporation, 1963-1968 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Porto Mills, Inc (Bravada Corp. P.R.), 1960-1969 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Prif Enterprises S.A., 1971 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Propper International Inc., 1967-1975 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Pueblo International Inc., 1970 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Puertex, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Puerto, Ltd., 1967 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Puerto Rican Clothing Co. Puerto Rico, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Puerto Rican Textiles, Ltd. (P.R.), 1953 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Puerto Rico American Tanning Co. (P.R.), 1956 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Puerto Rico Clothing Co. (P.R.), 1959-1970 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Puerto Rico Glove Co., Inc. (P.R.), 1956-1962 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- Puerto Rico Industrial Manufacturing Corporation. (P.R.), 1957-1966 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Puerto Rico Knitting Mills, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Porto Rico Needlework (P.R.), 1955-1958 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Puerto Rico Pants, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- Puerto Rico Safety Equipment Corp., 1970-1973 (Box 64, Folder 21)
- Puerto Rico Tanning Corp. (P.R.), 1957-1969 (Box 64, Folder 22)
- Puerto Rico Uniform and Garment Manufacturing Co. (P.R.), 1957 (Box 64, Folder 23)
- Puritan Sportswear Corporation., 1972 (Box 64, Folder 24)
- Puritan Comerio, Inc., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- Puritana Manufacturing Corp, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Pyramid Textile Manufacturing, Inc., 1968 (Box 64, Folder 27)
- Quilting, Inc., 1970 (Box 64, Folder 28)
- R.J. and D. Corp., 1969-1971 (Box 64, Folder 29)
- Ramon Jane, Inc., 1973 (Box 64, Folder 30)
- Randy Knitting Mills, Inc., 1972 (Box 64, Folder 31)
- Raymodes of P.R., Inc., 1976 (Box 64, Folder 32)
- Regina Apparel Co. (Sam Schweitzer) (P.R.), 1951 (Box 64, Folder 33)
- William Reilly, (Sawyer Tower Inc., Mass), 1961 (Box 64, Folder 34)
- Red Cape Leather Products Corp., 1960-1962 (Box 64, Folder 35)
- Ribbon Bow Corp. (P.R.), 1955 (Box 64, Folder 36)
- Ricardo Corp., 1962-1971 (Box 64, Folder 37)
- Rico Glove Corp. (P.R.), 1954-1971 (Box 64, Folder 38)
- Rio Grande Jacket Company, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 39)
- Rio Grande Manufacturing Corporation., 1956-1969 (Box 64, Folder 40)
- Rio Monte Manufacturing Corp., 1963-1969 (Box 64, Folder 41)
- Rio Rita Corporation, 1965-1969 (Box 64, Folder 42)
- Corporacion Rivera, Matos Inc., 1968 (Box 64, Folder 43)
- Rivera Silva-Miguel, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 44)
- Marcelino Cruz Rodriguez (P.R.), 1969 (Box 64, Folder 45)
- Roma Neckwear Corp., 1971 (Box 64, Folder 46)
- Ronnie Manufacturing Co. Corozal, P.R., 1959-1964 (Box 64, Folder 47)
- Ropa Sultana, Inc., 1968 (Box 64, Folder 48)
- Rosita Mills, Inc., 1962-1967 (Box 64, Folder 49)
- Royal Manufacturing Co., 1957-1963 (Box 64, Folder 50)
- S.P.R. Corporation (P.R.), 1959 (Box 64, Folder 51)
- St. Thomas Textiles Inc. (St. Thomas, V.I.), 1966 (Box 64, Folder 52)
- Sabana Grande Embroidery Co. (P.R.), 1957-1971 (Box 64, Folder 53)
- Sabana Grande Manufacturing. Corp., 1969 (Box 64, Folder 54)
- Sagner International Inc., 1963-1971 (Box 64, Folder 55)
- F. Lebron Saldana & Co., Inc., (P.R.), 1968-1969 (Box 64, Folder 56)
- Salinas Gloves, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 57)
- Salinas Manufacturing Corp. (P.R.), 1967-1968 (Box 64, Folder 58)
- Saliva, Gustavo (P.R.), 1956-1957 (Box 64, Folder 59)
- Saliva Soria Sisters, Inc., (P.R.), 1969 (Box 64, Folder 60)
- San Marcos Corporation, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 61)
- Sanrico Sportswear Inc. (P.R.), 1957 (Box 64, Folder 62)
- Guillermo Ruiz, Inc., 1967 (Box 64, Folder 63)
- Angel Suarez & Unos., Inc. (P.R.), 1969 (Box 64, Folder 64)
- Schweitzer Corp. (P.R.), 1956 (Box 64, Folder 65)
- Swiss Handloom, Inc. (See Santiago R. Palmer San German Needlework) (P.R.) (Box 64, Folder 66)
- Sea Breeze Knitwear Corp., 1963-1969 (Box 64, Folder 67)
- Isabela Sugunda Corp. (P.R.), 1963-1973 (Box 64, Folder 68)
- Sherman Classics (Hyman Sherman) (See file Cambridge Inc.,) (Box 64, Folder 69)
- Morris P. Sherman (Puerto Rico.), 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 70)
- Sira Glove Corp (Sub of Aris Gloves Corp N.Y.), 1967-1971 (Box 64, Folder 71)
- Siro Corp., (Puerto Rico), 1963 (Box 64, Folder 72)
- Sleep 'N Lounge Inc., (P.R.), 1967 (Box 64, Folder 73)
- Smartex Corp., 1963 (Box 64, Folder 74)
- Smith-Caribbean, Inc., (P.R.), 1969 (Box 64, Folder 75)
- Southland Manufacturing. Corp, 1960-1962 (Box 64, Folder 76)
- Southwood Knitting Mills, Inc., 1968 (Box 64, Folder 77)
- Spencer Manufacturing Co., Inc., (P.R.), 1953-1957 (Box 64, Folder 78)
- Sportee Corp. of America (P.R.), 1959-1962 (Box 64, Folder 79)
- Sports Caribe, Inc., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 80)
- Sportswear of Italy, Inc., 1976 (Box 64, Folder 81)
- Staple Manufacturing Corp. Hato Tedas, Bayamon, (P.R.), 1960-1969 (Box 64, Folder 82)
- Star Industries, Penneles, (P.R), 1966 (Box 64, Folder 83)
- Gerald Stempler and Associates, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 84)
- Stitchcraft International Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 64, Folder 85)
- Stobi International, Inc., 1977 (Box 64, Folder 86)
- Stratford of Puerto Rico, 1965-1971 (Box 64, Folder 87)
- Levi-Strauss Manufacturing de Puerto Rico, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 64, Folder 88)
- Sucesores de Angel Suarez, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 89)
- Sucesores De Blanes, Inc., 1971-1973 (Box 64, Folder 90)
- Suarez and Hermanos, Inc. (P.R.), 1953-1964 (Box 64, Folder 91)
- Sumac Cravat Inc. (P.R.), 1957-1963 (Box 64, Folder 92)
- Sunny-Isle, Inc. (P.R.), 1956-1957 (Box 64, Folder 93)
- Suntime Fashions, Inc. (P.R.), 1967 (Box 64, Folder 94)
- Superba Co. (Ponce, P.R.), 1974 (Box 64, Folder 95)
- Superior Knitting Corp., 1954 (Box 64, Folder 96)
- Surtex Glove Corp. (See Kayser-Roth Corp.) (P.R.), 1960-1970 (Box 64, Folder 97)
- Swimtex Corp., 1964-1969 (Box 64, Folder 98)
- Taco-Si de Puerto Rico, Inc., 1966 (Box 64, Folder 99)
- Technical Textiles Corp., 1973-1974 (Box 64, Folder 100)
- Tejidos Company, Inc., 1970 (Box 64, Folder 101)
- Tejidos Hermy, Inc., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 102)
- Tempo Glove Co. (P.R.), 1954-1964 (Box 64, Folder 103)
- Tex Products Manufacturing Corp., 1967 (Box 64, Folder 104)
- Texilease Manufacturing Corporation., 1971 (Box 64, Folder 105)
- Toa Manufacturing. Co., Inc., 1966-1971 (Box 64, Folder 106)
- Top Quality Corporation, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 107)
- Topeka Manufacturing, Inc., 1962-1964 (Box 64, Folder 108)
- Top Quality Corporation Cabo Rojo, P.R., 1963 (Box 64, Folder 109)
- Rogiguez Torres & Co. Inc., 1968 (Box 64, Folder 110)
- Towles, William, H., Inc. (P.R.), 1956-1971 (Box 64, Folder 111)
- Tremont Inc. Vauco, P.R., 1959-1960 (Box 64, Folder 112)
- Tropic Isle Novelty Corp. (P.R.), 1954 (Box 64, Folder 113)
- Tropicwear Industries, Inc. (P.R.), 1959-1973 (Box 64, Folder 114)
- Uclides Men's Shorts, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 115)
- United Corporation, 1961-1973 (Box 64, Folder 116)
- United Glove Corp., 1970 (Box 64, Folder 117)
- United Hosiery Mills Inc., 1971 (Box 64, Folder 118)
- United Sewing & Knitting Co., 1964-1971 (Box 64, Folder 119)
- Utuado Glove Corporation, 1967-1971 (Box 64, Folder 120)
- Utuado Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1971 (Box 64, Folder 121)
- Valtex, Inc., 1977 (Box 64, Folder 122)
- Van Hausen De P.R., Inc. (Aguadirla, Puerto Rico), 1964-1971 (Box 64, Folder 123)
- Van Raalte Co. Inc., 1960-1976 (Box 64, Folder 124)
- Vera Linen Manufacturing, Inc., 1976 (Box 64, Folder 125)
- Versalles Manufacturing. Corp., 1977 (Box 64, Folder 126)
- Vicente, Jose Vicente (P.R), 1958 (Box 64, Folder 127)
- Victory Pants, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 128)
- Isabella Vieques Corp., 1961-1977 (Box 64, Folder 129)
- Viola, M., 1972 (Box 64, Folder 130)
- Michael Viola, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 131)
- Viviana Fashions, Inc., 1975 (Box 64, Folder 132)
- W.C.R. Corporation, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 133)
- Wallart Manufacturing Corp., 1970-1971 (Box 64, Folder 134)
- Washable, Inc., 1966-1970 (Box 64, Folder 135)
- Milton Weinsten, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 136)
- Western Fashions, Inc., 1976 (Box 64, Folder 137)
- Western Garment Corp., 1968-1974 (Box 64, Folder 138)
- Wewstern Needlecraft, Inc. (P.R.), 1958 (Box 64, Folder 139)
- West Indies Manufacturing Co. Inc., (P.R), 1958-1961 (Box 64, Folder 140)
- West Island Manufacturing. Cp. Inc., 1964-1971 (Box 64, Folder 141)
- Western Garment Corporation, 1967-1969 (Box 64, Folder 142)
- Williams Corporation of P.R., 1932-1969 (Box 64, Folder 143)
- Wilrico, Inc., 1962-1969 (Box 64, Folder 144)
- Windsor Manufacturing Corp., 1974 (Box 64, Folder 145)
- Raimundo Zavala,- Winner Manufacturing, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 146)
- Johnathan Winson, 1958-1959 (Box 64, Folder 147)
- Wisco Fabric, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 148)
- Bert Wolf, (P.R.), 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 149)
- Wolverine World Wide, Inc,., 1969-1975 (Box 64, Folder 150)
- Winston Ely Corp. (See Cadillac Overall), 1958-1966 (Box 64, Folder 151)
- Work Clothes Manufacturing Co., Inc. Mayaguez, P.R., 1966 (Box 64, Folder 152)
- Zavala, Reimundo, 1964-1968 (Box 64, Folder 153)
- Zucker, Isaiah O. (P.R.), 1957 (Box 64, Folder 154)
- Richard C. Zuckerwar, 1961-1976 (Box 64, Folder 155)
- Montreal Arbitration - July, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- ACWA - Arbitration - Pittsburgh, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- ACWA - Arbitration Cases - New York Joint Board of Neckwear Workers, 1959 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- ACWA - Arbitration Cases - Canada, Montreal, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- ACWA - Arbitration Cases - Jay Garment Co., 1946-1954 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- ACWA Arbitration Cases - Picardy Mills, 1953 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- ACWA - Arbitration Cases - Canada, Toronto, 1953 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- ACWA - Arbitration Cases - Canada, Montreal, July., 1953 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- ACWA - Arbitration Cases - Canada, Montreal & Toronto, 1952 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- ACWA - Arbitration Cases - New York & New Jersey Cleaning & Dyeing Co., 1949-1952 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- ACWA - Arbitration Cases - Canada, Montreal, 1943-1949 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- ACWA - Arbitration Cases - Cleaners and Dyers Board of Trade, 1941-1943 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- ACWA - Arbitration Cases - Canada, 1935-1942 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- IUD - Insurance and Pension Plans, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- ACWA - Recreational Services, 1951-1960 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO - Anti-Inflation Conference, 1978-1979 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- ACWA - Press Releases, 1954-1972 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- ACWA - E Press Releases, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- ACWA - F Press Releases, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- ACWA - E Press Releases, 1951 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- ACWA - F Press Releases, 1950 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- ACWA News, 1961-1962 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- ACWA News, 1960-1963 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- ACWA - NLRB and Court Cases - Grunwald-Marx, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Action, 1975-1976 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Action, 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- ACWA Public Affairs - Election Campaigns, 1975-1976 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- ACWA Political Action - Election Campaigns, 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- ACWA Strikes, Lockouts, and Injunctions, 1975-1977 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- ACWA - Arbitration Cases Pittsburgh, Pa. - May, 1957 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- ACWA - Arbitration Cases - Pittsburgh, Pa., 1953 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- BLS - Archive, 1950-1960 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Material on Wage and Price Freeze, 1971-1973 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- ACWA Material on Wage and Price Freeze, 1971-1973 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Textile Division Synthetics, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Textile Division General, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- ACTWU - Textile Div. - Elections, 1972-1977 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Textile Division - Broad-Woven Fabrics, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Phillips-Van Heusen, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Organizing South, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Economic Opportunity Act - Training Projects, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Workmen's Compensation - New York, 1957-1958 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Business Week-Reprint of article on "Labor Violence and Corruption." August 31. Together with correspondence with regard to the article. (Potofsky, Lubin, Bell, and Carmody), 1957 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Burlington Studies, 1968-1973 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Obituaries for GEB Report, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- VF: Poses, Lillian, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- ACWA Historical Material Comments on ACW: General and Favorable, 1975-1976 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Film "Inheritance", 1976 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- ACWA International Activities Foreign Travel by ACWA Officials, 1975-1976 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated International Activities Foreign Travel by ACW Officials, 1973-1974 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- ACWA International Activities ACW Statements on Foreign Policy, 1975-1976 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated International Activities ACWA Statements on Foreign Policy, 1973-1974 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- ACWA International Activities Foreign Visitors to ACWA, 1975-1976 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated International Activities Foreign Visitors to ACWA, 1973-1974 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- ACWA International Activities Amalgamated. Projects Abroad, 1975-1976 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- ACWA International Activities International Labor Unity and ILO, 1975-1976 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated International Activities. International Labor Unity and ILO, 1973-1974 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- Out of Business, 1976-1977 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- Plant Sale, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- Plant Shutdown, 1974-1975 (Box 68, Folder 20)
- Plant Closing, 1971-1972 (Box 68, Folder 21)
- Plant Closing, 1970-1973 (Box 68, Folder 22)
- Relocation of Firms, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 23)
- ACTWU Archive - "807" Mexico Program, 1966-1972 (Box 68, Folder 24)
- ACTWU Official's Writings Archive, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 25)
- Men's & Boys' Apparel Mergers, 1954-1961 (Box 68, Folder 26)
- Rainwear-Rainfair Case, 1950-1957 (Box 68, Folder 27)
- Aged: Health Care: King-Anderson Bill, 1963-1965 (Box 68, Folder 28)
- ACTWU Publications, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 29)
- Arbitration Cases CMA re Col clause in '74 contract, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 30)
- ACWA Arbitration Cases Chicago retail negotiations, 1969-1972 (Box 68, Folder 31)
- ACWA - Arbitration Cases - Cluett, Peabody & Co. Atlanta, Georgia, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 32)
- ACWA Arbitration - Fruhauf Southwest Garment Company - Wichita, Kansas, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 33)
- ACWA Arbitration Montreal Joint Board, 1964 (Box 68, Folder 34)
- Obituaries, 1968-1979 (Box 68, Folder 35)
- Unemployment Insurance, 1921-1954 (Box 68, Folder 36)
- A Study of Absenteeism and the Reduced Work Week in Individual Clothing Plants throughout the US (Archive), 1963 (Box 68, Folder 37)
- Taxation to 1959 (Box 68, Folder 38)
- Guaranteed Employment and Wage Plans to 1949 (Box 68, Folder 39)
- Veterans' Employment Rights, 1949 (Box 68, Folder 40)
- Economic Opportunity Act of 1964, 1964-1972 (Box 68, Folder 41)
- Men's Clothing Survey New York City & New Jersey - Fall Season, 1936 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated. Strikes, Lockouts and Injunctions News clippings, 1973-1976 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- ACWA - Organizing Activities, 1952-1984 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- ACWA Convention - Washington, D.C - June, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Wage Increases, Men's Clothing, 1975-1977 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Wage Increases, Outerwear Cloth Coats & Jackets Leather Coats & Jackets, 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Wage Increases Shirts, Nightwear & Underwear, 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Wage Increases Other Cotton Garments, 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Wage Increases Rainwear, 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Wage Increases Neckwear, 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Wage Increases Gloves, 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Wage Increases Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Wage Increases, Wage Negotiations Men's Clothing, 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Wage Increases, Cleaning & Dyeing - Laundry, 1972-1974 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Wage Increases & Negotiations Cotton Garments and Outerwear, 1972-1974 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Wage Increases Gloves, 1974-1975 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Wage Increases Single Pants & Outerwear, 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 13)
- Wage Increases Retail, 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 14)
- Wage Increase & Negotiations, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- Wage Increases: Cleaning & Dyeing & Laundry, Neckwear, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 16)
- Wage Increases Retail, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 17)
- Wage Increases & Negotiations Cotton Garments + Outerwear, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Wage Increases: Men's Clothing, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Wage Increases: Single Pants & Outerwear, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 20)
- Wage Increases: Misc., 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 21)
- Wage Negotiations & Increases, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 22)
- Wage Negotiations & Increases Cotton Garment and Outerwear Negotiations, 1972-1975 (Box 70, Folder 23)
- Wage Negotiations Men's Clothing, 1974 (Box 70, Folder 24)
- Amalgamated Wage Increases, 1968-1969 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Wage Increases, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Wage Negotiations and Increases Men's Clothing, 1971-1972 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Wage Increases & Negotiations Cotton Garments, 1967-1968 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Wage Increases & Negotiations Men's Clothing, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Men's and Boys' Apparel + Wages, 1947-1971 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Shirts and Pajamas - Wages, 1953-1968 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Tailored Suits, Etc - Wages, 1957-1969 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Tailored Suits, Etc. - Wages - Survey of 4 New York Cutting rooms, January, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Gloves - Fabric and Leather Dress - Wages and Hours, 1950-1963 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Men's and Boys' Apparel - Prices, 1925-1974 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Shirts and Pajamas - Prices, 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Tailored Clothing - Prices, 1942-1947 (Box 71, Folder 13)
- Apparel - Production, 1938-1973 (Box 71, Folder 14)
- Men's and Boys' Apparel - Production, 1929-1975 (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Shirts and Pajamas - Production, 1953-1962 (Box 71, Folder 16)
- Shirts and Pajamas - Productivity, 1953-1959 (Box 71, Folder 17)
- Tailored Suits…Production, 1954-1979 (Box 71, Folder 18)
- Productivity - Tailored Clothing, 1951-1970 (Box 71, Folder 19)
- Apparel Industry Men's and Boys' Apparel Imports, 1957-1978 (Box 71, Folder 20)
- ACWA - Collective Bargaining, 1945-1958 (Box 71, Folder 21)
- ACWA - Collective Bargaining (Cotton Garment Industry), 1959 (Box 71, Folder 22)
- ACWA - Cleaners and Dyers Joint Board, 1959-1977 (Box 71, Folder 23)
- ACWA - Bushelman, 1960-1964 (Box 71, Folder 24)
- ACWA - Bushelmen's Wages, 1960-1969 (Box 71, Folder 25)
- ACWA - Cleaning and Dyeing - Prosperity Cleaners, 1965-1966 (Box 71, Folder 26)
- ACWA - Union Shop Bankruptcies and Migrations, 1959-1965 (Box 71, Folder 27)
- ACWA - Employment, 1940-1963 (Box 71, Folder 28)
- ACWA NLRB Cases, 1975-1976 (Box 71, Folder 29)
- Amalgamated N.L.R.B. Cases, 1973-1974 (Box 71, Folder 30)
- Wage Increase Textiles, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 31)
- Wage Increases & Negotiations Cotton Garments, 1975-1976 (Box 71, Folder 32)